Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University Records Documenting Bicycling
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Athletics, Yale University, records documenting bicycling
1902-1984
RU 509
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.75
(2 boxes)
The records consist of news clippings, memoranda, and photographs documenting bicycling at Yale.
Yale University. Dept. of Athletics, Physical Education, and Recreation
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 38-B (YRG 38-B), Records documenting specific sports at Yale.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by type of material.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of news clippings, memoranda, and photographs documenting bicycling at Yale.
College sports; Cycling; Yale University Athletic Association; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University. Dept. of Athletics, Physical Education, and Recreation
- Clippings, memorabilia, and photographs of the bicycling team, 1902, 1938-1984; Accession 1986-A-101
  - Clippings
    - 1938-1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1967-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - no date (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Memorabilia
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - pre-1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1969-1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1976-1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - no date (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Photographs
    - circa 1902 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - 1959 (Box 2, Folder 18 - 19)
    - Slides, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - 1960 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 1961-1967 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - no date (Box 2, Folder 23 - 26)